[{"id":0,"question":"1+2","choices":[2,3,4],"rightAnswer":3,"qOperator":"+","difficultyLevel":1,"isPassed":false,"isCorrect":false},{"id":1,"question":"7+8","choices":[13,15,16],"rightAnswer":15,"qOperator":"+","difficultyLevel":1,"isPassed":false,"isCorrect":false},{"id":2,"question":"4+5","choices":[8,9,10],"rightAnswer":9,"qOperator":"+","difficultyLevel":1,"isPassed":false,"isCorrect":false},{"id":3,"question":"2+3","choices":[4,5,6],"rightAnswer":5,"qOperator":"+","difficultyLevel":1,"isPassed":false,"isCorrect":false},{"id":4,"question":"6+4","choices":[9,10,11],"rightAnswer":10,"qOperator":"+","difficultyLevel":1,"isPassed":false,"isCorrect":false},{"id":5,"question":"8+7","choices":[13,15,16],"rightAnswer":15,"qOperator":"+","difficultyLevel":1,"isPassed":false,"isCorrect":false},{"id":6,"question":"3+6","choices":[8,9,10],"rightAnswer":9,"qOperator":"+","difficultyLevel":1,"isPassed":false,"isCorrect":false},{"id":7,"question":"5+4","choices":[8,9,10],"rightAnswer":9,"qOperator":"+","difficultyLevel":1,"isPassed":false,"isCorrect":false},{"id":8,"question":"7+2","choices":[8,9,10],"rightAnswer":9,"qOperator":"+","difficultyLevel":1,"isPassed":false,"isCorrect":false},{"id":9,"question":"9+6","choices":[14,15,16],"rightAnswer":15,"qOperator":"+","difficultyLevel":1,"isPassed":false,"isCorrect":false},{"id":10,"question":"1+8","choices":[8,9,10],"rightAnswer":9,"qOperator":"+","difficultyLevel":1,"isPassed":false,"isCorrect":false},{"id":11,"question":"4+6","choices":[9,10,11],"rightAnswer":10,"qOperator":"+","difficultyLevel":1,"isPassed":false,"isCorrect":false},{"id":12,"question":"3+7","choices":[8,9,10],"rightAnswer":10,"qOperator":"+","difficultyLevel":1,"isPassed":false,"isCorrect":false},{"id":13,"question":"5+3","choices":[8,9,10],"rightAnswer":8,"qOperator":"+","difficultyLevel":1,"isPassed":false,"isCorrect":false},{"id":14,"question":"2+9","choices":[10,11,12],"rightAnswer":11,"qOperator":"+","difficultyLevel":1,"isPassed":false,"isCorrect":false},{"id":15,"question":"6+8","choices":[13,14,15],"rightAnswer":14,"qOperator":"+","difficultyLevel":1,"isPassed":false,"isCorrect":false},{"id":16,"question":"1+7","choices":[7,8,9],"rightAnswer":8,"qOperator":"+","difficultyLevel":1,"isPassed":false,"isCorrect":false},{"id":17,"question":"4+2","choices":[5,6,7],"rightAnswer":6,"qOperator":"+","difficultyLevel":1,"isPassed":false,"isCorrect":false},{"id":18,"question":"9+4","choices":[12,13,14],"rightAnswer":13,"qOperator":"+","difficultyLevel":1,"isPassed":false,"isCorrect":false},{"id":19,"question":"3+5","choices":[7,8,9],"rightAnswer":8,"qOperator":"+","difficultyLevel":1,"isPassed":false,"isCorrect":false},{"id":20,"question":"15+7","choices":[21,22,23],"rightAnswer":22,"qOperator":"+","difficultyLevel":2,"isPassed":false,"isCorrect":false},{"id":21,"question":"8+12","choices":[18,20,21],"rightAnswer":20,"qOperator":"+","difficultyLevel":2,"isPassed":false,"isCorrect":false},{"id":22,"question":"14+9","choices":[22,23,24],"rightAnswer":23,"qOperator":"+","difficultyLevel":2,"isPassed":false,"isCorrect":false},{"id":23,"question":"18+6","choices":[23,24,25],"rightAnswer":24,"qOperator":"+","difficultyLevel":2,"isPassed":false,"isCorrect":false},{"id":24,"question":"9+16","choices":[26,25,28],"rightAnswer":25,"qOperator":"+","difficultyLevel":2,"isPassed":false,"isCorrect":false},{"id":25,"question":"13+8","choices":[20,21,22],"rightAnswer":21,"qOperator":"+","difficultyLevel":2,"isPassed":false,"isCorrect":false},{"id":26,"question":"17+5","choices":[22,23,24],"rightAnswer":22,"qOperator":"+","difficultyLevel":2,"isPassed":false,"isCorrect":false},{"id":27,"question":"9+14","choices":[20,21,23],"rightAnswer":23,"qOperator":"+","difficultyLevel":2,"isPassed":false,"isCorrect":false},{"id":28,"question":"15+6","choices":[19,20,21],"rightAnswer":21,"qOperator":"+","difficultyLevel":2,"isPassed":false,"isCorrect":false},{"id":29,"question":"8+17","choices":[25,25,28],"rightAnswer":25,"qOperator":"+","difficultyLevel":2,"isPassed":false,"isCorrect":false},{"id":30,"question":"21+7","choices":[27,28,29],"rightAnswer":28,"qOperator":"+","difficultyLevel":2,"isPassed":false,"isCorrect":false},{"id":31,"question":"16+6","choices":[27,22,30],"rightAnswer":22,"qOperator":"+","difficultyLevel":2,"isPassed":false,"isCorrect":false},{"id":32,"question":"19+8","choices":[25,27,28],"rightAnswer":27,"qOperator":"+","difficultyLevel":2,"isPassed":false,"isCorrect":false},{"id":33,"question":"14+3","choices":[22,17,25],"rightAnswer":17,"qOperator":"+","difficultyLevel":2,"isPassed":false,"isCorrect":false},{"id":34,"question":"18+7","choices":[24,25,26],"rightAnswer":25,"qOperator":"+","difficultyLevel":2,"isPassed":false,"isCorrect":false},{"id":35,"question":"3+19","choices":[29,30,22],"rightAnswer":22,"qOperator":"+","difficultyLevel":2,"isPassed":false,"isCorrect":false},{"id":36,"question":"20+8","choices":[28,30,32],"rightAnswer":28,"qOperator":"+","difficultyLevel":2,"isPassed":false,"isCorrect":false},{"id":37,"question":"15+4","choices":[24,25,19],"rightAnswer":19,"qOperator":"+","difficultyLevel":2,"isPassed":false,"isCorrect":false},{"id":38,"question":"13+7","choices":[20,27,28],"rightAnswer":20,"qOperator":"+","difficultyLevel":2,"isPassed":false,"isCorrect":false},{"id":39,"question":"9+18","choices":[25,26,27],"rightAnswer":27,"qOperator":"+","difficultyLevel":2,"isPassed":false,"isCorrect":false},{"id":40,"question":"27+46","choices":[68,73,73],"rightAnswer":73,"qOperator":"+","difficultyLevel":3,"isPassed":false,"isCorrect":false},{"id":41,"question":"58+47","choices":[105,104,105],"rightAnswer":105,"qOperator":"+","difficultyLevel":3,"isPassed":false,"isCorrect":false},{"id":42,"question":"76+89","choices":[156,164,165],"rightAnswer":165,"qOperator":"+","difficultyLevel":3,"isPassed":false,"isCorrect":false},{"id":43,"question":"35+68","choices":[101,103,103],"rightAnswer":103,"qOperator":"+","difficultyLevel":3,"isPassed":false,"isCorrect":false},{"id":44,"question":"47+62","choices":[109,109,109],"rightAnswer":109,"qOperator":"+","difficultyLevel":3,"isPassed":false,"isCorrect":false},{"id":45,"question":"59+78","choices":[134,137,137],"rightAnswer":137,"qOperator":"+","difficultyLevel":3,"isPassed":false,"isCorrect":false},{"id":46,"question":"49+86","choices":[135,134,135],"rightAnswer":135,"qOperator":"+","difficultyLevel":3,"isPassed":false,"isCorrect":false},{"id":47,"question":"68+79","choices":[146,147,147],"rightAnswer":147,"qOperator":"+","difficultyLevel":3,"isPassed":false,"isCorrect":false},{"id":48,"question":"55+73","choices":[126,128,128],"rightAnswer":128,"qOperator":"+","difficultyLevel":3,"isPassed":false,"isCorrect":false},{"id":49,"question":"72+67","choices":[139,139,139],"rightAnswer":139,"qOperator":"+","difficultyLevel":3,"isPassed":false,"isCorrect":false},{"id":50,"question":"63+57","choices":[119,120,120],"rightAnswer":120,"qOperator":"+","difficultyLevel":3,"isPassed":false,"isCorrect":false},{"id":51,"question":"54+88","choices":[140,142,142],"rightAnswer":142,"qOperator":"+","difficultyLevel":3,"isPassed":false,"isCorrect":false},{"id":52,"question":"75+64","choices":[137,138,139],"rightAnswer":139,"qOperator":"+","difficultyLevel":3,"isPassed":false,"isCorrect":false},{"id":53,"question":"86+78","choices":[152,163,163],"rightAnswer":163,"qOperator":"+","difficultyLevel":3,"isPassed":false,"isCorrect":false},{"id":54,"question":"48+73","choices":[120,121,121],"rightAnswer":121,"qOperator":"+","difficultyLevel":3,"isPassed":false,"isCorrect":false},{"id":55,"question":"68+56","choices":[123,124,124],"rightAnswer":124,"qOperator":"+","difficultyLevel":3,"isPassed":false,"isCorrect":false},{"id":56,"question":"89+74","choices":[161,163,163],"rightAnswer":163,"qOperator":"+","difficultyLevel":3,"isPassed":false,"isCorrect":false},{"id":57,"question":"57+89","choices":[144,145,146],"rightAnswer":146,"qOperator":"+","difficultyLevel":3,"isPassed":false,"isCorrect":false},{"id":58,"question":"74+78","choices":[152,153,154],"rightAnswer":152,"qOperator":"+","difficultyLevel":3,"isPassed":false,"isCorrect":false},{"id":59,"question":"65+87","choices":[150,151,152],"rightAnswer":152,"qOperator":"+","difficultyLevel":3,"isPassed":false,"isCorrect":false},{"id":60,"question":"326+74","choices":[399,400,400],"rightAnswer":400,"qOperator":"+","difficultyLevel":4,"isPassed":false,"isCorrect":false},{"id":61,"question":"198+85","choices":[272,283,283],"rightAnswer":283,"qOperator":"+","difficultyLevel":4,"isPassed":false,"isCorrect":false},{"id":62,"question":"453+68","choices":[519,521,521],"rightAnswer":521,"qOperator":"+","difficultyLevel":4,"isPassed":false,"isCorrect":false},{"id":63,"question":"365+79","choices":[431,444,444],"rightAnswer":444,"qOperator":"+","difficultyLevel":4,"isPassed":false,"isCorrect":false},{"id":64,"question":"547+68","choices":[615,616,616],"rightAnswer":616,"qOperator":"+","difficultyLevel":4,"isPassed":false,"isCorrect":false},{"id":65,"question":"472+85","choices":[547,557,557],"rightAnswer":557,"qOperator":"+","difficultyLevel":4,"isPassed":false,"isCorrect":false},{"id":66,"question":"639+74","choices":[701,712,712],"rightAnswer":712,"qOperator":"+","difficultyLevel":4,"isPassed":false,"isCorrect":false},{"id":67,"question":"584+68","choices":[648,652,652],"rightAnswer":652,"qOperator":"+","difficultyLevel":4,"isPassed":false,"isCorrect":false},{"id":68,"question":"327+85","choices":[402,412,412],"rightAnswer":412,"qOperator":"+","difficultyLevel":4,"isPassed":false,"isCorrect":false},{"id":69,"question":"598+79","choices":[671,672,672],"rightAnswer":672,"qOperator":"+","difficultyLevel":4,"isPassed":false,"isCorrect":false},{"id":70,"question":"437+68","choices":[505,506,506],"rightAnswer":506,"qOperator":"+","difficultyLevel":4,"isPassed":false,"isCorrect":false},{"id":71,"question":"326+89","choices":[405,416,416],"rightAnswer":416,"qOperator":"+","difficultyLevel":4,"isPassed":false,"isCorrect":false},{"id":72,"question":"598+74","choices":[671,672,672],"rightAnswer":672,"qOperator":"+","difficultyLevel":4,"isPassed":false,"isCorrect":false},{"id":73,"question":"421+85","choices":[496,506,506],"rightAnswer":506,"qOperator":"+","difficultyLevel":4,"isPassed":false,"isCorrect":false},{"id":74,"question":"376+68","choices":[444,444,445],"rightAnswer":444,"qOperator":"+","difficultyLevel":4,"isPassed":false,"isCorrect":false},{"id":75,"question":"254+79","choices":[321,333,333],"rightAnswer":333,"qOperator":"+","difficultyLevel":4,"isPassed":false,"isCorrect":false},{"id":76,"question":"583+74","choices":[656,657,657],"rightAnswer":657,"qOperator":"+","difficultyLevel":4,"isPassed":false,"isCorrect":false},{"id":77,"question":"739+68","choices":[806,807,807],"rightAnswer":807,"qOperator":"+","difficultyLevel":4,"isPassed":false,"isCorrect":false},{"id":78,"question":"612+74","choices":[686,688,688],"rightAnswer":688,"qOperator":"+","difficultyLevel":4,"isPassed":false,"isCorrect":false},{"id":79,"question":"845+68","choices":[913,913,914],"rightAnswer":913,"qOperator":"+","difficultyLevel":4,"isPassed":false,"isCorrect":false},{"id":80,"question":"423+678","choices":[1101,1100,1101],"rightAnswer":1101,"qOperator":"+","difficultyLevel":5,"isPassed":false,"isCorrect":false},{"id":81,"question":"587+349","choices":[934,936,936],"rightAnswer":936,"qOperator":"+","difficultyLevel":5,"isPassed":false,"isCorrect":false},{"id":82,"question":"712+495","choices":[1197,1198,1199],"rightAnswer":1197,"qOperator":"+","difficultyLevel":5,"isPassed":false,"isCorrect":false},{"id":83,"question":"846+273","choices":[1118,1119,1120],"rightAnswer":1119,"qOperator":"+","difficultyLevel":5,"isPassed":false,"isCorrect":false},{"id":84,"question":"935+287","choices":[1222,1222,1223],"rightAnswer":1222,"qOperator":"+","difficultyLevel":5,"isPassed":false,"isCorrect":false},{"id":85,"question":"769+476","choices":[1235,1245,1245],"rightAnswer":1245,"qOperator":"+","difficultyLevel":5,"isPassed":false,"isCorrect":false},{"id":86,"question":"594+321","choices":[915,915,916],"rightAnswer":915,"qOperator":"+","difficultyLevel":5,"isPassed":false,"isCorrect":false},{"id":87,"question":"836+479","choices":[1315,1316,1317],"rightAnswer":1315,"qOperator":"+","difficultyLevel":5,"isPassed":false,"isCorrect":false},{"id":88,"question":"721+594","choices":[1315,1316,1317],"rightAnswer":1315,"qOperator":"+","difficultyLevel":5,"isPassed":false,"isCorrect":false},{"id":89,"question":"967+438","choices":[1404,1405,1405],"rightAnswer":1405,"qOperator":"+","difficultyLevel":5,"isPassed":false,"isCorrect":false},{"id":90,"question":"846+729","choices":[1575,1575,1576],"rightAnswer":1575,"qOperator":"+","difficultyLevel":5,"isPassed":false,"isCorrect":false},{"id":91,"question":"923+698","choices":[1619,1620,1620],"rightAnswer":1620,"qOperator":"+","difficultyLevel":5,"isPassed":false,"isCorrect":false},{"id":92,"question":"758+681","choices":[1439,1440,1440],"rightAnswer":1440,"qOperator":"+","difficultyLevel":5,"isPassed":false,"isCorrect":false},{"id":93,"question":"645+739","choices":[1374,1375,1375],"rightAnswer":1375,"qOperator":"+","difficultyLevel":5,"isPassed":false,"isCorrect":false},{"id":94,"question":"892+765","choices":[1656,1657,1657],"rightAnswer":1657,"qOperator":"+","difficultyLevel":5,"isPassed":false,"isCorrect":false},{"id":95,"question":"723+986","choices":[1699,1709,1709],"rightAnswer":1709,"qOperator":"+","difficultyLevel":5,"isPassed":false,"isCorrect":false},{"id":96,"question":"978+846","choices":[1824,1825,1825],"rightAnswer":1825,"qOperator":"+","difficultyLevel":5,"isPassed":false,"isCorrect":false},{"id":97,"question":"834+965","choices":[1787,1788,1788],"rightAnswer":1788,"qOperator":"+","difficultyLevel":5,"isPassed":false,"isCorrect":false},{"id":98,"question":"956+729","choices":[1685,1686,1686],"rightAnswer":1686,"qOperator":"+","difficultyLevel":5,"isPassed":false,"isCorrect":false},{"id":99,"question":"789+945","choices":[1715,1725,1725],"rightAnswer":1725,"qOperator":"+","difficultyLevel":5,"isPassed":false,"isCorrect":false}]